Guide to the Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
Archives Union File (AUF), Section 6: Boxes 319.1-378
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 375, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: A summary of basic wage rates and hours for Chauffeurs and Helpers in the greater St. Louis area, Publication (Box 375, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: Teamsters / All-Star Benefit Boxing Show for the St. Louis Polio Foundation, Publication (Box 375, Folder 5)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 376, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Dispute concerning jurisdiction submitted for determination to Joint Council #16 pursuant to Article IX, Section 12,., Publication (Box 376, Folder 1)
  - Item 2: Table Q - R -- New York City Family Income (1959), Publication (Box 376, Folder 1)
  - Item 3: Table 1 -- Variable and constant (1947-49).Dollar change 1958 to 1960, average weekly earnings, manufacturing production workers, 17 major population centers, 1947-1960 (Box 376, Folder 1)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 376, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Meeting the challenge of health care today; a study and a first-step program., 1963; Publication (Box 376, Folder 2)
    Author: Columbia University. School of Public Health and Administrative Medicine
    Notes: Teamsters Joint Council No. 16 and Management Hospitalization Trust Fund. 2 copies
  - Item 2: Better Health Bulletin, 1962; Publication (Box 376, Folder 2)
    Author: Joint Council No. 16 (New York, N.Y.)
    Notes: Jun-62
  - Item 3: For release: College-educated Negroes in New York State, employed in jobs usually, Publication (Box 376, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Teamster News Release: New York City's relatively inferior wage position is not limited to manufacturing production, Publication (Box 376, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: New York State Unemployment: the Rockefeller fictions and the facts, Publication (Box 376, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: New York State income growth: Harriman vs. Rockefeller, Publication (Box 376, Folder 2)
    Notes: Press release. 2 copies
  - Item 7: New York is not the Empire State in the field of educational attainment, Publication (Box 376, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Employment growth in New York State in the first three years of Harriman and Rockefeller, Publication (Box 376, Folder 2)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 376, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: The decline and fall of Governor Rockefeller's Empire State, Publication (Box 376, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Governor Rockefeller's fiscal integrity fact or fraud, Publication (Box 376, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: New York State factory wages: the Rockefeller myth vs the reality, Publication (Box 376, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Lindsay '66 + Lindsay '67 = Social Chaos and Fiscal Disaster, Publication (Box 376, Folder 3)
  - Item 5: Governor Rockefeller is bankrupting New York, Publication (Box 376, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Annual report of Joint Council No. 16 (1964), Publication (Box 376, Folder 3)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 376, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: TCP Newsletter, 1966-1967 (Box 376, Folder 4)
    Notes: Apr, June, Sept. 1967; Oct 1966
  - Item 2: New York city personal income and population totals as per cent of New York State totals, 1950-1956 (Box 376, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: New York City's share of the nonfarm employment totals of both the nation and the metropolitan area continues to decline, Publication (Box 376, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: This union respectfully urges your committee to recommend to the legislature that the State of New York take over both the local, Publication (Box 376, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Teamster Center News - a typical day at the Teamster Center, Publication (Box 376, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: The Teamster Center at Montefiore Hospital, Publication (Box 376, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Diagnosis and consultation, health advisory services surgery for specific conditions, Publication (Box 376, Folder 4)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 376, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: A contemporary analysis of a labor union, Publication (Box 376, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: Lindsay '66 + Lindsay '67 = Social Chaos and Fiscal Disaster, Publication (Box 376, Folder 5)
    Notes: Press release. 2nd copy
  - Item 3: Affluent or hard-working society? White family income United States, 1967, Publication (Box 376, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Abandonment, illegitimacy & Dependency New York City, 1958-1968 (Box 376, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: No fun for workers in John Lindsay's fun city, Publication (Box 376, Folder 5)
  - Item 6: Collective bargaining is not enough, Publication (Box 376, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Taxpayers wanted - Long hours-Hard work-No pay: Apply to John V. Lindsay, Publication (Box 376, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Suburban affluence: for whom?, Publication (Box 376, Folder 5)
  - Item 9: The enemy within: illegitimacy in New York City, Publication (Box 376, Folder 5)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Old challenges and new horizons for U.S. unionism, 1962; Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
    Author: Harold J. Gibbons
    Notes: Joint Council of Teamsters, No. 13. 2 copies
  - Item 2: Organizing the unorganized shop, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Recommendations for a health program for unions, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: an experiment in medical care, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: What is a union?, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Chester Bowles: danger in our foreign policy, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
    Notes: Flyer 2nd copy
  - Item 7: James Roosevelt: the nature of trade union power, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: Teamster Center News, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
  - Item 9: Teamster Center News, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 3, no. 2, 4- 5
  - Item 10: Teamster Center News, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 4, no. 1-4
  - Item 11: Teamster Center News, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 5, no. 1- 4
  - Item 12: Teamster Center News, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 6, no. 1, 6-8
  - Item 13: Teamster Center News, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: Teamster Center News, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 8, no. 1- 3
  - Item 15: Teamster Center News, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 9, no. 1-2
  - Item 16: Teamster Center News, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 10, no. 1- 2
  - Item 17: Teamster Center News, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: Teamster Center News, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 12, no. 1- 2
  - Item 19: Teamster Center News, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 13, no. 1, 3
  - Item 20: Teamster Center News, Publication (Box 376, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 14, no. 1
- U.S. Congression, Publication (Box 377, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: US Congressional and Legislative Facts, Publication (Box 377, Folder 1)
    Notes: first annual
  - Item 2: US Congressional and Legislative Facts, Publication (Box 377, Folder 1)
    Notes: second annual
  - Item 3: US Congressional and Legislative Facts, Publication (Box 377, Folder 1)
    Notes: third annual
- U.S. Congression, Publication (Box 377, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Statement before the General Subcommittee on Labor of the Education and Labor Committee of the U.S. House of Representatives - Statement by, Publication (Box 377, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Statement before Select Subcommittee on Labor United States House of Representatives - Statement by Sidney Zagri, Publication (Box 377, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Congressional and Legislative Facts (93rd Congress, 1973-74), 1973-1974 (Box 377, Folder 2)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 377, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: To: General Executive Board, General Organizers, Joint Councils, Local Unions, and DRIVE Directors, Publication (Box 377, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Statement before Platform Committee, Republican National Convention, Publication (Box 377, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Labor needs your vote, Publication (Box 377, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: I'm Registered to Vote! Are you?, Publication (Box 377, Folder 3)
    Notes: Bumper sticker
  - Item 5: Action series in Practical Precinct Politics (workshop folder with pamphlets), Publication (Box 377, Folder 3)
  - Item 6: Testimony on the National Highway Safety Act, Publication (Box 377, Folder 3)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 377, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Local 174 vs. Lucas Flour Company -- On writ of Certiorari to the Washington Supreme Court, Publication (Box 377, Folder 4)
    Author: Local 174
  - Item 2: Commercial Car Journal (CCJ) The Magazine of Fleet Magazine, 1965; Publication (Box 377, Folder 4)
    Notes: Aug. 1965
  - Item 3: Automotive Teamster, Publication (Box 377, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 7, no. 2-4
  - Item 4: Automotive Teamster, Publication (Box 377, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 8, no. 1-6
  - Item 5: Automotive Teamster, Publication (Box 377, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 9, no. 1-3
  - Item 6: Automotive Teamster, Publication (Box 377, Folder 4)
    Notes: Vol. 10, no. 1-4
  - Item 7: Automotive Teamster, Publication (Box 377, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 11, no. 1-3
  - Item 8: Automotive Teamster, Publication (Box 377, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 12, no. 1-3
  - Item 9: Automotive Teamster, Publication (Box 377, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 13, no. 1-4
  - Item 10: Automotive Teamster, Publication (Box 377, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 14, no. 1-2
  - Item 11: Automotive Teamster, Publication (Box 377, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 15, no. 1-2
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 378, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Teamster Newsletter, Local 287, 1957; Publication (Box 378, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1957 (Mar-Apr, Sept)
  - Item 2: Teamster Newsletter, Local 287, 1959; Publication (Box 378, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1959 (May-July, Sept-Oct)
  - Item 3: Teamster Newsletter, Local 287, 1960; Publication (Box 378, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1960 (Jan- Dec)
  - Item 4: Teamster Newsletter, Local 287, 1961; Publication (Box 378, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1961 (Jan-Feb, Apr-June)
  - Item 5: Teamster Newsletter, Local 287, 1962; Publication (Box 378, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1962 (Dec)
  - Item 6: Teamster Newsletter, Local 287, 1963; Publication (Box 378, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1963 (Apr- June)
  - Item 7: Teamster Newsletter, Local 287, 1965; Publication (Box 378, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1965 (Feb- Mar)
  - Item 8: Teamster Newsletter, Local 287, 1966; Publication (Box 378, Folder 1)
    Notes: 1966 (Mar- Nov)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 378, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Teamster Newsletter, Local 287, 1957; Publication (Box 378, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1957 (Mar-Apr, Aug, Nov-Dec)
  - Item 2: Teamster Newsletter, Local 287, 1958; Publication (Box 378, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1958 (Jan-Aug, Oct-Dec)
  - Item 3: Teamster Newsletter, Local 287, 1959; Publication (Box 378, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1959 (Jan)
  - Item 4: Teamster Newsletter, Local 287, 1961; Publication (Box 378, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1961 (Mar, Sept- Dec)
  - Item 5: Teamster Newsletter, Local 287, 1962; Publication (Box 378, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1962 (Jan-Feb, Apr-July, Sept-Nov)
  - Item 6: Teamster Newsletter, Local 287, 1963; Publication (Box 378, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1963 (Feb-Mar, May-June, Oct)
  - Item 7: Teamster Newsletter, Local 287, 1964; Publication (Box 378, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1964 (Feb)
  - Item 8: Teamster Newsletter, Local 287, 1965; Publication (Box 378, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Teamster Newsletter, Local 287, 1966; Publication (Box 378, Folder 2)
    Notes: 1966 (Mar-May, July-Nov)
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 378, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Teamsters 445 Dispatch, Publication (Box 378, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 4, no. 9, 11-13
  - Item 2: Teamsters 445 Dispatch, Publication (Box 378, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 5, no. 2-14
  - Item 3: Teamsters 445 Dispatch, Publication (Box 378, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 6, no. 3, 11-13
  - Item 4: Teamsters 445 Dispatch, Publication (Box 378, Folder 3)
    Notes: vol. 7, no. 2, 4-6
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 378, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Teamsters 445 Dispatch, Publication (Box 378, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 7, nos. 8-13
  - Item 2: Teamsters 445 Dispatch, Publication (Box 378, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 8, no. 1-4, 9, 11, 12
  - Item 3: Teamsters 445 Dispatch, Publication (Box 378, Folder 4)
    Notes: vol. 9, no. 1-2, 4-5
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 378, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Teamsters 445 Dispatch, Publication (Box 378, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 9, no. 7-11
  - Item 2: Teamsters 445 Dispatch, Publication (Box 378, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 10, no. 1-2, 4-5, 7-9, 11-12
  - Item 3: Teamsters 445 Dispatch, Publication (Box 378, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol 11, no. 1, 8-9, 12
  - Item 4: Teamsters 445 Dispatch, Publication (Box 378, Folder 5)
    Notes: vol. 12, no. 1, 3, 6-8
- International Brotherhood of Teamsters, Chauffeurs, Warehousemen, and Helpers of America, Publication (Box 378, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Teamsters 445 Dispatch, Publication (Box 378, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 12, no. 1-7, 9
  - Item 2: Teamsters 445 Dispatch, Publication (Box 378, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 13, no. 2, 4-8
  - Item 3: Teamsters 445 Dispatch, Publication (Box 378, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 14, no. 1-3
  - Item 4: Teamsters 445 Dispatch, Publication (Box 378, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Teamsters 445 Dispatch, Publication (Box 378, Folder 6)
    Notes: vol. 16, no. 1, 5